emedevents.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy | eMedEvents

**eMedEvent's Privacy Policy Statement**

**Purpose of eMedEvents's Privacy Policy -**  Our privacy statement explains the ways we collect any information and how we use it and our commitment to respect your information.

**Personal information -**  Personal information that is provided by the users includes the user name, email address, telephone number, Zip code and credit card numbers. Information we may collect that's not provided by you directly includes your IP address, Location information, and Device and browser information. We also collect data about usage patterns, search queries. We may use the information to create personal profiles to improve the functionality.

**Use of personal information -**  We use the information gathered to provide better service that is aligned to individual preferences. We also measure traffic patterns to provide individualized content. We generate summary reports based on user data for our advertisers but we provide them only anonymous information. We use third party advertisers like to Google, Bing to provide ads on our website. You can visit the respective ad websites to know more about their privacy policies.

We may approach you periodically with offers, products and services that may be of interest to you based on your usage preferences. If you wish not to be contacted, please unsubscribe from the list. We may require users to register to use the website, the information provided will be stored electronically. We may provide the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests which are voluntary. But by entering the competition, you give us permission to use the personal information to notify the winners, to promote it on the website. If these are organized by third party providers, we may prohibit them from using the personal information without your consent.

We may provide forums, reviews on the website and this information is public. We may send emails, product notifications via email periodically and the user has the choice to unsubscribe from them at any time. We deploy software called Cookies to better understand how users interact with the website. We may have relations with various advertisers and firms who place their ads on the website. They deploy cookies as well and we have no control over the information collected by them and bear no responsibility. We also use web beacons that help us deliver content that is of more interest to the individual user. These are embedded in the website and we do not tie them to your personal information. We may also provide avenues for interactive services to better engage the user and provide a unique experience. We may also provide personal information to law enforcement under applicable laws.

We request you to provide feedback on our services so we can better serve you and this information will not be shared with anyone. We provide links to various websites and we are not responsible for the content, privacy policies of any third party websites.

Our privacy policies may change over time to keep up with regulations, new laws and they will be posted here.

##### View Conference Details
